export const cards = [
    {
        front: " == ",
        back: "loose equality comparison operator, which means it will try to convert the operands to the same type before comparing them",
        level: [1]   
    },
    {
        front: " === ",
        back: "strict equality comparison operator, which means it will only return true if the operands are of the same type and have the same value.",
        level: [1]
    },
    {
        front: "addEventListener",
        back: "a method is used to attach an event handler function to an element on a web page. This allows the function to be executed when a specific event occurs, such as a user clicking on a button.",
        level: [1]
    },
    {
        front: "Boolean",
        back: "a data type that has only 2 values: true or false",
        level: [1]
    },
    {
        front: "Variable",
        back: "a container for storing a value, such as a number, string, or object.",
        level: [1]
    },
     {  front: "Function",
        back: "a block of code that performs a specific task. It can be called multiple times with different arguments.",
        level: [1]
    },
    {
        front: "Array",
        back: "a collection of elements, such as numbers, strings, or objects, stored in a single variable.",
        level: [1]
    },
    {
        front: "Object",
        back: "a collection of key-value pairs, used to store and manipulate complex data.",
        level: [1]
    },
    {
        front: "Operator",
        back: "used to perform mathematical or logical operations on values, such as addition, subtraction, or comparison.",
        level: [1]
    },
    {
        front: "Conditional statement",
        back: "examples are if/else or switch and allow you to execute different code based on a certain condition.",
        level: [1]
    },
    {
        front: "Loops",
        back: "examples are for or while and allow you to repeat code multiple times based on a certain condition.",
        level: [1]
    },
    {
        front: "Event",
        back: "actions or occurrences, such as a mouse click or page load, that trigger JavaScript code to execute.",
        level: [1]
    },
    {
        front: "DOM Manipulation",
        back: "a programming interface for HTML documents that allows you to manipulate elements and content on a web page using JavaScript.",
        level: [1]
    },
    {
        front: "String",
        back: "a sequence of characters, such as 'hello' or 'world', that can be manipulated using various string methods in JavaScript.",
        level: [1]
    },
    {
        front: "Comments",
        back: "they are used to add notes or explanations to code. They are ignored by the browser and do not affect the code's functionality.",
        level: [1]
    },
]